Can I use the mileage?
Mileage?
Possibly to America but you are
20,000 miles short.
Then, how far can I go with it?
Pardon?
Excuse me for a minute.
Hello. This is PARK Man-Soo.
When can I expect the money
you borrowed from me?
sorry?
I didn't borrow any money.
Aren't you the PARK Man-Soo
who directed the City of Scream?
Yes, I am the director PARK Man-Soo.
You borrowed 200,000 dollar
to make that movie.
But I am a director.
Directors are the ones who make movies?
We have business to discuss.
Well, I am at the Inchon airport
about the board the plane.
Sure, Sure. Look across the street.
Eh?
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I have nothing to do with
the financial matters of the movie.
Isn 't it illegal
to just kidnap someone like this?
We don't know the detail.
We bring you to
the boss when he wants
and send you away
when he's done with you
Send me away? Where?
Where you wanna go?
Patagonia.
Where?
It means big foot.
Bit foot.
to the end of the world.
On the other side of the globe...
it is said to be a great place.
Big foot?
You should be specific like Underground,
in the sea, in the mountain...
then we can take care of it.
Where?
Under the ground,
or in the sea or mountain.
I really have no financial
responsibility about.
Some big mouth you got,
son of a bitch!
I would like to send him away.
I could do no such thing, Sir.
He is my dad.
That old man.
He is from high land
of Gaema in Hamgyoungdo.
He's left home missing
for the tenth time.
You know such condition for
old people.
Al... Almond...Al Pacino...
Alzheimer?
Whatever.
Anyway, he's a little off.
It's about time to go.
It's embarrassing since
it's a domestic matter.
So I would like to send him away.
Sir, I understand the difficulties
dealing with sick old man.
But you cannot possibly
think of such horrible thing.
You are a bit slow
for a movie director, eh?
To Gaema plateau.
I would like to send him there.
Anything's possible in a movie.
Find a similar sight and put up a sign
that says Gaema plateau.
One picture there would make
him happy.
Souvenir, you know.
Old people pass time
looking at photos.
You're not lying?
'Be straight!'
If you don't want to, never mind.
What a handsome picture.
Uh... my... my passport.
Don't worry.
Just keeping it for you.
I'll need that.
Go!
Do you have a new project
offered yet?
How about a thriller this time
rather than erotic picture?
Corpses buried in the mountain...
cut in pieces.
Floating pieces of flesh
on the ocean.
With a mysterious woman.
Scary, isn't it?
Hey, what are you doing snatching
the ball from children?
What kind of grown up are you?
What?
Let's go kids.
I must've waken you up. Sorry.
What bring you here?
We're going to see grandpa Bae.
But we're not ready yet.
Get ready on the way.
PARK Soo-dong
Grandpa Pear! How are you?
Where you going again?
Where do you want me to take you?
- Come on, kid! Let's go.
- What's going on with you?
- Let's go. Move your ass.
Well, sir, where you going?
Hold on.
- Sir!
- Let's go.
- Move!You lazy boy. Hurry up.
- Sir.
- Let's go. Just walk.
- But where are you going to?
Sir.
- Hey! You've got to tell me where?
- Let's go. Let's go!
- Look!
- Let's go!
Sir!
Dad, you drunk again? Huh?
Think of Mom.
What are you here for?
- you half wit, sly rat.
- Sir, what's wrong?
You rat
I don't want that money!
Hey!
Go inside, or I'll hit you.
Go inside!
He's like that sometimes.
But it's a good sign that
he thinks you are his son.
No way.
I look nothing like him.
At least one of rat,
half wit,
or snitch.
Nothing difficult really,
if you think about it.
By the way, you were rude
to speak to him that way.
Well, he listens to me, at least.
How can I go with him
when he hates his son so much.
No father hates his son,
just can't bear him to be disgraceful.
Can I ask you something?
Shoot.
The doorplate says that his name is PARK,
why do you call him Granpa Pear?
Our director has a sharp sense.
The story goes that when
he first showed signs of Alzheimer
we took him to the hospital.
Sir. Which one of these is an apple?
Can you pick up an apple?
apple!
So we called him Grandpa Pear since.
He is getting much worse recently.
You've been lying all along.
Hey! Not you too.
Despite all,
you don't owe them money and
tricking people isn't filmmaker's job.
Sit down. Continue.
So we're filming?
No, we go on as if making a movie.
What if we get caught?
I know little of it
so I'll leave that up to you.
Wait!
You see, making a movie requires
much preparation and a lot of people
have to come together.
Do you know Al Pacino?
He's an actor who played a blind man
in the Scent of Women. A blind man.
There is a scene
where he falls while dancing.
When he was about to fall, he finds
a big nail sticking out on the ground.
Well, he is supposed to be blind.
So he fell on the nail.
Oh, shit! So? He got pricked?
I'd love to meet this guy.
- Who?
- That Al... Al...
the blind buy with a nail stuck
in the eye.
What I am trying to say is
that it is not easy to trick people.
Hold on, let me take care of some business
then tell me the rest.
Ah, that scum bag!
That piece of shit!
Spare me. Ouch! Agh!
What's the boss' moto? Be straight!
Date and time is quite plain and clear.
He hates people
who can't keep their time.
- you promised to pay back today
- Please don't kill me!
and I promised I will send you away
if you don't.
At least I'll keep my word.
Close it!
Hey! Hey!
Mail it.
When you fight or scare people,
don't look in their eyes.
Eyes make you weak.
I don't like fighting at all.
Neither do I.
We have something in common.
Ah, I told Grandpa Pear that he got permission
to go to North Korea in a weak.
That old man sure wants to go home.
What? In a week?
- Is it a problem?
- No... well, it's kind of...
Kind of? Problem or no problem?
It's not a problem but I could surely use
more time to get things in order...
Be straight! Problem or no problem?
So,
it is not a problem but realistically
there are much to be done ahead...
Make up your mind.
I am not smart enough for such complications.
Just tell me if it is a problem
or no problem. What is it?
No problem!
Fine. Then it's a deal.
Keep your promise
if you don't want to be sent away.
I will.
Hello.
True Hamheung noodle is only served
in North Korea.
If it is made with the Hangang river water,
it is Hangang noodle not Hamheung noodle.
We guarantee the best quality service to
Grandpa PARK Soo-dong
including a nice female companion.
Can you speak North Korean?
Try North Korean dialect.
I couldn't fake it.
I lived only a short life
to summarize in a few words.
Overcoming the 50 years of separation
since independence...
We didn't even pay them the guarantee
for the last movie.
I brought them with promise of casting
for the next movie.
Go ahead. Let's see what you got.
Have you had a big breakfast?
You will need a full stomach to walk
around the home town.
I will make it
a mission to lead you...
She is Korean-Chinese from the border.
Sounds just right. Try singing?
In the sky...
- how did I do?
- Yeah, OK.
What's with that guy?
Hey, you!
You are not allowed in here.
You are a prop.
Outside! Now!
Uhh... LEE Sung-Chul
of Na-tional secu-rity,
at your service.
You must follow my instruc...tions
to en...sure a safe trip.
Thank you.
There is something I must ask you.
What?
I need a car but
the budget can't cover it.
What kind of car?
All of them drive Benz.
We cannot drive South Korean car.
- how many?
- Just one will do.
- Consider it done.
- Alright.
Why can't I just say 'let's go'
No way. He will get suspicious.
Congratulation/ Mr. PARK Soo-Dong's
visiting to hometown in North Korea.
Aren't you the PARK's son?
Ah yeah, how are you?
Time changed you so. I can't recognize you at all.
Wow, completely different person.
- Is dad inside?
- He's gone.
- Gone where?
- Maybe yesterday?
Maybe today.
He said he's going to his hometown.
Where? Hometown, where?
Dad!
Hey!
We've met once before, remember?
We should get to your hometown.
I'm not going.
If you don't go, I'm a dead meat.
No! I'm not going.
Ey! You think you will better
off without me?
Are you out of your mind?
No way I'm taking you.
I'm going with you.
I'm the one who has been putting
food in your mouth.
Ok. I won't go.
Woman, you've finally gone mad.
You are going there to see Gab-bun.
You think I don't know that?
Let go.
I said I'm not going.
I am not going.
- We have to go now.
- I'm not going. No.
Are you OK?
Oh, you were here.
Take this with you. I want you to give
these photos to my kids there.
I don't know
if we'll have such time for...
I miss them so much.
No. I won't go!
- His head popped!
- Dad. Dad!
- Please, don't forget. I really miss them.
- I'll make sure they get it, of course.
Dad! Dad! Wait up!
Bon voyage!
What?
I can't connect with Sung-Chul.
What am I gonna do with Benz?
Never mind. We'll take any car.
I'm hanging up.
Man-Soo, what's wrong with me?
Why have you done wrong?
Why let them harass you like this?
It's not my fault that
the movie flopped.
Do I get rich if the movie sells?
My dream has nothing to do with
gangster's father realizing his dream.
Why can't I be left alone?
Here we are.
Let's get off now.
- Hand me your bag.
- Don't touch it.
Just over that line,
is North Korea.
Are you Ok sir?
No! Call the Ambulence!
No. I am fine.
I have to go. Go over.
Are you parents alive, then?
Well, that's...
Dead? Alright.
Come with me then.
Shoot, I was told
never to open my mouth.
We must go.
Are you Ok sir?
Wellcome, comrade PARK Soo-Dong.
Welcome home!
Comrade Grandpa!
Welcome!
The car isn't here yet.
What?
We can go now.
Comrade Grandpa!
I hope you had a big breakfast.
You'll need the full stomach
for the busy day ahead.
Big day, it is.
I will accompany you to
your hometown so not to worry.
Please get in the car, now.
Please get in the car.
Let's move.
Comrade driver,
he's new in the job.
Please understand, comrade grandpa.
We haven't got all day.
Comrade, let's get to the highway.
Hurry.
Shit!
Finally, Grandpa KIM Soo-dong, no,
PARK Soo-dong comes back to
his hometown in 50 years!
20 million people of Chosun Republic!
Let's welcome him!
Hey, diver.
You'd better ask me, dad.
Why did you come after me?
I'm your son.
Why did you tag along,
when you should be studying?
So I am still your son, dad?
Comrade Grandpa.
You can ask me whatever you want.
Take me to this place.
There are many villages like this.
t looks like where I grew up.
What's your name, miss?
ou shouldn't call her miss, dad.
Oh, no never mind,
Comrade Grandpa.
My name is YEON Hong-Mae.
Hong-Mae. Yes. Hong-Mae,
can you take me there?
No. We have other place to go.
Take me there.
You said you will take me home.
Comrade Grandpa, don't worry.
What do you mean, don't worry?
I am sorry.
Driver, take me there,
would you?
Yes. Sure.
What do you mean, sure?
That will cost a fortune.
Fuck! We just say we go!
They say we can go.
Stupid moron.
- I'll see about that.
- No!
013503, 013503, black Benz
vehicle information please.
I'll have to see that.
No, not you!
Comrade Grandpa, why don't you
let him see the picture.
Let me take a look.
Here. We have to get there.
They don't know where it is.
We have a tour planned out already.
You, ingrate! Give me back
the watch you stole!
Watch?
3503, Black Benz, pull over.
Stop the car!
Why don't we pull over?
3503 Pull over to the side. Now!
Stop the car.
They will stop following at some point.
- Comrade Grandpa, are you OK?
- Okay.
You, good for nothing,
you hit somebody? What did you do?
Just beg for forgiveness.
Tell them you are sorry.
But, I didn't do anything wrong.
Stop the car.
Let's stop the car.
Stop the car now!
I said stop!!
Have you gone deaf?
Pull over to the side!
Who the hell are you?
Good day, officer.
I can explain everything.
Just calm down.
Pathetic piece of crap,
I knew it.
Not a day goes by without trouble.
Hopeless!
This wouldn't stop us from
going to the village?
Not at all. You have nothing to worry.
You people are looking for trouble.
There are laws and principles.
Who will keep the order of our nation
if all the displaced people
pull off such thing?
Don't you see the news?
There are innumerable applicants
waiting to go to North Korea.
Do they respect the law
out of stupidity?
Why is this guy so quiet?
He doesn't talk much.
Listen.
If all the passers-by
pick the flowers
on the street,
there will be none left.
Huh?
You look old enough to have
such common sense.
How old are you?
And that!
Display of such flag is against the law.
Which country do you belong to?
3503 Stolen vehicle! Stolen!
- you are under arrest.
- you stole this car?
- You Fucker!
- Oh, my, are you nuts?
What are you doing!
I am 34 years old.
What's your business in that?
Stop it!
Are you nuts?
Officer! open your eyes!
In the middle of the freezing cold winter,
what flower!
You son of a bitch!
Does this look like a flower to you?
Are you crazy?
Officer are you OK?
Officer!
You son of a bitch!
You're really going mad, know.
Let me go.
Get out of my way!
Are you OK?
Get in the car. In the car!
What flower?
Hurry up.
Let's get out of here.
Damn it!
Start the car!
How can you bring a stolen car?
I told you I borrowed it.
What is going on?
Just tell them you are sorry.
You good for nothing!
34 years means you were born
with sign of rat.
Why?
I am 35, Pig.
So?
Just telling you.
Oh no. what are we going to do?
- Grandpa has wet His pants...
- I'm ok. It's fine.
- Grandpa!Are you OK?
- I'm ok.
First? It's me.
Dad, get out of the car.
Let's get you changed.
I'm ok.
Give me your bag.
No way I step out of the car.
You try to get rid of me?
- Give me the bag.
- Not a chance.
Let him be.
I think you're Ok.
Who do you think you are?
What are you trying to pull here?
This kind of village might be all over
where you come from,
but to recreate that here cost a fortune.
I am sorry.
I don't need an uncontrollable mouth
like you. Go home.
Mr. Director,
we should still get him to change
his pants.
He must be cold in those wet pants.
Let's get him changed first...
I must ask you a favor.
Shoot!
It is rather to clarify
the situation.
This trip strictly has to follow
my instruction.
I am the one who takes responsibility
when something goes wrong.
So you mean, you are the boss.
No, it's not about being a boss.
I'm talking about the responsibility.
So you are not the boss?
It is not the issue of who is the boss.
It seems like you are the boss.
I'm gonna crazy!
What's wrong with this guy!
Is that the only way to explain
the world to you?
There are more things in the world.
So you want to be the boss,
the point is.
Fine! I am the boss and you
are just along for a ride.
But my life depends on this.
Life? Right!
That's cool, boss.
I'm going mad.
Hey, Lieutenant, feeling comfy?
Get up!
I'll get them car thieves.
Where? Stop right there.
Yes, I missed this taste.
Hanheung noodle is original here.
If you make it with Han Gang river water,
it'd only be Hang Gang noodle.
Don't you agree, Comrade Grandpa?
Where are you from?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Excuse me, do you have
anything to drink?
Dad, no. No alcohol.
Why not. A drink to go along with the food
he missed so much.
You little rat. She says it's OK.
What's it to you?
Wow, nice atmosphere. Huh?
Redecorated the place?
If you were to make a movie,
you first should've
gotten permission.
Why did you have to come to our town
to turn it into North Korea?
People in this village died to protect
their home during Skull battle,
Eagle peak battle,
and what else?
- What?
- Haengju battle.
Yeah, did you hear that?
What is this?
This is not our food.
Where is ostrich meat?
That's what we are famous for.
Yeah, the ostrich.
Ostrich!
Oy! You fatzo!
You laughing at me? Huh?
Ouch! You're gonna hit me?
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
Who is the director? I need to be
compensated for emotional distress.
Why don't you tell me.
This is not your place to get involved.
Which one of you is the director?
Don't you know that we are working
for unification of the country.
You are too small beat up.
What is the guy?
Guys, sit down. Don't run.
You should take responsibility of your action.
Wow, you must be an actress, sugar!
Stupid jerk,
who said you can call me like that.
Didn't your mother teach you
how to behave?
Marines aren't supposed to mess
with women.
- Shut your face!
- Oh my.
You should consider yourselves lucky.
My parents died in
Manchuria fighting the Japanese.
What kind of life is that?
Come and have a drink with me.
- Wow, the actress is buying.
- Good!
Here, give us five bottles of
Soju and squid.
Soju? What for?
Goryangju 20 bottles please.
Bottoms up!
Drink.
Hey, Ostrich!
Aren't you sleeping, yet?
Are you awake?
How do you feel?
I displayed quite an embarrassing scene
tonight, I guess.
Not at all.
Look, Grandpa, look.
There is no more programs for tonight.
Let me watch it.
Today's program is over.
You, son of a bitch!
Do you have something to tell me?
I wanted to say thank you.
- Don't mention it.
- Director PARK.
- What?
You should go see Grandpa Pear
in his room.
- What?
- you should go see in His room.
I just want to catch up with the news
of my home town.
Holy shit.
Comrade Grandpa insists on watching TV.
There is no stopping him.
Boss.
- Start setting up.
- Yeah. Huh?
Shooting, shooting. Get up!
Ugh... what shooting?
Get ready in two minute.
Wake up,
What's this?
You are going to help me.
Out of the way.
You're blocking the TV.
Yes. Dad. It's working now.
Today, Grandpa PARK Soo-Dong arrived
through Panmunjeom to visit his home town.
People who witnessed this historical moment
were overcome by tears of joy.
This is how one of them
expressed her welcome.
I just wish you take some good photos
when you go.
- And enjoy your Hanheung noodle.
- Thank you. Thank you.That was delicious...
Welcome. Let me introduce you
the famous Ostriches of North Korea.
This one's Southy and that's Northy.
I can sing.
I can fly to the sky.
I am stronger than you.
I am not really an ostrich but a crane.
- If you are a crane, I am a dragon.
- I am God.
I am the red devil.
How come you are the red devil.
This is what their fight had come to.
quack
Let's not fight.
Finally, we will finish today's program
with a visual message from South Korea.
We wish you a pleasant dream.
I miss you sister.
Your name is PARK Ok-Rye
and I am PARK Ok-Soon.
I've missed you so much
my one and only sister.
You must not die until the day
we meet and hold hands.
I wait for our reunion
day and night.
Live long so we can meet. I miss you.
That's our village on TV.
That's where we are.
Hah, our town's on TV.
- Yes, boss.
- Everything's going well?
Everything is going well.
Good work.
What's up?
But I am afraid we'll need
more money though.
- What money?
- We need to build a little village.
Did you screw up?
Movies aren't made easy.
We have to put our lives on the line.
Who's dead?
No, no one got killed.
- I mean, we put our lives to complete...
- you think you are a movie director?
Do your job and keep your eyes
on the rat next to you.
Sure thing boss.
- Be straight!
- I understand.
It isn't easy to trick him.
My father never held my hand.
I only feared him and
wished him dead.
He passed away a few years ago.
I must be getting
punished right now.
Have you ever held
your father's hand?
I'm an orphan.
No one is here yet?
Chop chop!
hurry up
you have to memorize this lines.
- Nothing for me?
- You're a prop.
I don't have a line.
You cannot handle it.
First, how is it going?
We are ready as ever be. Perfect.
You've been doing a wonderful job.
Let's hold out one more day.
- Fighting!
- Fighting.
- Photographer?
- Yeah.
Not here yet?
What was perfect then?
What kind of nude photography shoot
is in such early hour?
hello
Who's in charge?
A terrible thing happened.
- Why?
- Comrade Grandpa has disappeared.
What?
He's not there?
- have you seen him?
- No.
Grandpa?
Some strange old man was looking for
some Gamma park or something.
Which way did he go?
I told him I don't know where that is.
Some clever guy.
Don't go anywhere.
Hey!
Where are you going, dad?
You shouldn't wander around alone.
Who are you?
Half wit, sly rat, stupid moron son.
I've come to take you
to your home town.
Liar! You? My son?
Don't you think
I'd recognize my own son?
Come clean.
You sold that watch, didn't you?
Comrade Grandpa, Comrade Grandpa.
Take me home.
They won't let me see my home town.
Let's go. We're almost there.
Just over that hill.
Yes. It's time to go to your home town.
Gaema Plateau.
Dad. We are here.
Here is Gaema Plateau.
Come and see.
This is Gaema national park.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Comrades,
let us enjoy the view of Gaema plateau.
It is nice here.
Let's take a picture.
Over here.
Excuse me,
where is Pungsan village?
Where?
Dad. Let's take a picture.
A picture? What for?
Comrade Grandpa,
this is Gaema Plateau.
Do you like it?
Yes. You must bring back
a photo and
remember to come back later.
Comrade Grandpa,
this is a good spot for a photo.
Take a picture.
Dad, stand here...
great.
Hong-Mae,
this is not the place.
You said...
You said you will take me
to this place.
Yes we'll go after you
take the picture.
Dad, we only got permission
for taking picture here.
She says we can go.
I have to go.
Dad, I understand.
Say something to him.
Well, let's go.
What?
What did you say?
How can you say something you
cannot take responsibility for.
- We'll just go.
- where can We find such place now?
You said somewhere's
gotta be like that.
I'm gonna crazy.
I told you movie is not that easy.
You can't just cut
in and make decisions.
I cannot carry out
my job like that.
Your job is to take him
to his home town.
You should've said this
from the beginning.
He says this is not it.
He'll listen to you.
You can take care of it.
I don't know anymore.
- I can't
- Why can't you, now?
We go if he wants to go.
You're not making sense.
Fuck.
He is the father of our boss.
Do whatever you want.
I don't know now.
You! Why you have so much
to say about everything?
Watch it.
You never done a movie?
Who's your agent?
A movie is made only
when actors follow
the director's order
You must trust him.
- Isn't it, director PARK?
- Some nutcase...
What did you say?
Seriously...
don't make me upset.
Well? You jerk!
Go ahead, hit me!
make off
- Let's see who hurts who.
- What's gotten into you? Stop.
hit me!
- Director! Director!
- Why?
- We have to wrap.
- Why do We have to wrap?
You, bastard!
It doesn't depend on you
Come here!
Hey!
Why can't you stop
hitting people?
- Why don't you hit again?
- Come here!
- Hit me!
- What are you, bitch!
They want to go home. They say they will
leave unless they get paid now.
- I said I'll pay them.
- We don't have the money.
We spent all of
it to build the sets.
Hey!
Keep working,
I'll get the money
Shut your face,
you think you are the director?
You are crazy acting like
you are in charge.
Stop please.
I'm begging you.
I am sorry.
This kid doesn't know
how the world works.
He always uses trick
and live loosely in South Korea.
- You got it wrong. Please!
- You rat!
Don't come if you don't want to.
This half wit, sly rat, moron.
We'll go without him.
Yes. Let's go.
Stupid son of a bitch,
still hasn't come to your sense?
- You don't know anything!
- Fuck. I can't take this anymore.
Here we are, everyone,
this is Gaema Plateau.
We came here.
There seems to be
a film shoot.
You can stay for
a while and take pictures.
What the hell is that?
- What the hell...
- Hey, hey!
Get lost!
This isn't your playground.
Son of bitch!
Why are youguys come in a band
and mess around, son of bitch!
Stupid sons of bitches.
Get in the bus
or you'll get slapped.
Son of bitches!
Where are you going?
Where are you going? Huh?
Where? Take me with you.
- where are We going?
- to get money.
Your boss said no.
Even if we get the money
how can we find a studio?
That man.
Who?
Al... with a nail in the eye.
Al Pacino?
What does he do nowadays?
You can't just barge
in demanding money, you know?
He doesn't pay even
when we ask him.
He's certainly not going to
pay when we do nothing.
He's always got cash.
can I ask you something?
What?
Grandpa Pear keeps talking
about the watch.
What is it?
A watch?
Ah that watch.
The story goes.
He learned to fix watches...
from a man with a wen.
While he was at it...
he also fell in love with
his daughter Gab-Bun.
You half wit, sly rat, moron.
Grandpa Pear soon
became skillful
and traveled around
the country fixing clocks.
Unfortunately...
the war broken
when he was working in Seoul.
That watch given by
the dying teacher is
the only thing that connected
him to his home.
He couldn't go back.
Since then, he married
in South Korea and had a son.
But he couldn't adapt to his new life.
It was't a good influence to a kid.
He probably wore
his father's watch
to the beach as a teenager
and lost it.
He still takes us to
the beach every year
and makes us look for the watch.
What is it?
What's going on?
How have you been, KIM?
What we have here?
Seong-Chul?
What brings you here in
such late hour.
Pay me back some money.
- What money?
- Money you borrowed.
It is not due till a month later,
you crazy son of a bitch.
Still, give me the money.
This is not what we agreed.
Agreement?
You told me to be straight
and punctual.
Sorry I am late, boss.
What the hell, communists!
Agreement can be broken.
You, son of bitch!
What the fuck are you doing
bitch!
You're mad. Insane!
I did wrong.
Put it in the bag.
What What?
Get the money.
You son of bitch!
Come here.
Get the money quickly.
I'll explain it
to the boss later, OK?
What agreement?
Nobody agreed for you
to be born?
- Stupid motherfucker!
- You son of bitch!
Now, run.
You said you have
money to collect.
This is stealing not collecting.
You've got a big mouth.
I don't want to get shot.
They are following us.
Throw the money.
They are getting on my nerves.
Go away before I count to three.
One two three.
Why are you doing this!
He is coming closer, towards us.
You want a face to face?
Brace yourselves, here I come.
That's Benz.
Youth knows no turning back.
Drive on.
Are you nuts?
Risking your life for money?
If you are willing to put
your life to it,
- you always win.
- Life? Life?
The fucking life!
This shit is not worth my life.
I have lots of things yet to do.
I still have to go to Patagonia,
make a movie.
Do you think I have to
risk my life for it?
- this shit?
- Yes, this shit!
You mean that?
Yeah! of course I mean it.
What?
You're gonna send me away?
There's mountain, snow
and water here.
Pick your favorite.
Send me away!
You'd better stop.
PARK Man-Soo.
I am not finished.
Try and stop me.
Don't come here.
You bitch!
Don't come near me.
- Let's go.
- I am Not going there.
- I won't do it. Stay away from me.
Scared of me?
Come on!
- No. keep away.
- We don't have a time.
I'll throw it to you
- Let's stop and go.
- No. I'm not going.
- You are asking to be sent away.
- go head. where to? Just try.
Throw it.
Send me away.
- go ahead
- you think I cannot do it?
- go ahead, pathetic fool
- I'll throw it to you
- go ahead
- Ah, shit!
Are you alright?
Let's go.
Are you really OK?
You son of a bitch!
Come here!
- Come here
- Stay away!
- Motherfucker
- Don't come! Don't come!
OK, OK.
my bad.
What have I done wrong?
You certainly did nothing good.
To make a movie
You put your life to it, you said!
Who put their life on the line
for only a movie?
What?
It sure sounds good
but no movie is worth my life.
it is not worth it?
Where are you going?
Wait for me!
Hold on! Wait up! Hey!
Wait up!
Hey! Wait up!
Call the police.
- Hurry up.
- Yeah, Yeah.
Where are they headed?
Gaema Plateau.
- where?
- Gaema Plateau.
Gaema Plateau?
Where's that club?
We are working to make money,
we are not going to work...
another minute
if we don't get paid.
Listen, listen.
Money, school both important.
But what about the human dignity?
By the way, is it true that
Seong-Chul is a gangster?
Yes, I am scared of him.
They're coming!
What?
You've got nothing better to do
than fighting all day?
What happened to your face?
I am sorry about early.
I was out of line.
Not at all.
You are really something.
I couldn't find any studio space.
No way at all?
They are rented
for a week already.
- You should've begged.
- It's not available.
After all I've gone through
to get this money.
I don't want to take pictures.
Suit yourself.
Take me home.
OK...
I'll make sure you get there.
Sir, take me home please.
What's wrong dad?
- Sir, take me home please.
- Comrade Grandpa, are you alright?
Come here, please!
- Sir!
- Comrade Grandpa!
Comrade Grandpa, are you OK?
- What's wrong?
- Let me go.
Sir, where are you going?
Hey.
Which way is the Gaebau Hill?
Up over that hill.
Give me a ride, would you?
Hop on.
I am not myself.
What?
I keep seeing things.
It's not good, is it?
Don't say that.
Have ever heard the sound of...
flowers blooming
in Gaema plateau?
It is so cold there that
the flowers pop open all at once.
The Gaeshtang tree white flowers,
I used to picked them and eat.
The sound of
the falling flowers is amazing.
Patter, patter
You have got to witness it
once in your life.
Here we are.
It's over that bridge.
They don't let people
in there nowadays.
Mother,
your son Soo-dong is here.
Stay there,
I'll come to you, mother.
your son Soo-dong is here.
Mother,
My baby.
Let me see your face.
My baby. You bastard.
I tried to come here, early
I tried.
however, who's that boy?
Who is that boy?
He's my son.
Come and bow to
your grandmother.
Bow to your grandmother.
He's got a job and
soon to be married
and settle down in Seoul.
You sly son of a rat.
You remarried?
No. No.
No. I would take Gab-Bun...
where did she go?
What the hell are you people?
- Fuck!What are you?
- Fuck?
- you scared the shit out of me.
- We're playing survivor game.
You scared me.
You are fake
but we are real people.
Have you seen Grandpa?
- No, I haven't.
- What? where did He go?
- He went That way.
- where, where?
- You bastards!
- Where, son of bitch!
Stop!
Movies you know.
Audience wants
something more shocking...
Why don't you shut
your mouth and...
Come near to me.
- turn your head.
- like this?
Close your eyes
and don't worry.
Have you seen Grandpa?
Hello?
I'm calling
from Survival game park.
What?
Gaster from North Korea?
Black Benz.
Ask if there was
a North Korean flag on the car?
Did they have the North Korean
flag on the car?
- Dad!
- Grandpa Pear!
Grandpa Pear!
Dad! Where would we find him?
We've come too far.
You are a gaster
who lost the father of the boss.
That sounds bad!
Stop talking, kid.
- Grandpa Pear!
- Grandpa!
- Dad!
They might be here to catch us.
What the hell did we do wrong?
We cannot get caught now.
I've still got to make the movie...
Shut your mouse
- Dad!
- Grandpa Pear!
Grandpa Pear!
Hop on quickly
Run! Fast!
- where are we?
- No idea.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Yes, sir.
- Seong-Chul there?
- one moment.
Hey, this is boss.
- Yes, boss.
- Hey, you bastard.
Did you beat up a cop?
And robbed a club?
Yes. Yes. It's no big deal.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Hold on, boss.
Take it.
- No.
- you tell him
You're the good liar among us.
Hello?
- Movie director!
- Yes, it's me.
So how is it going?
Yes. Everything is going very well.
Seon-Chul seems to
have caused trouble.
What happened to my old man?
- Grandpa is fine.
- Really?
Then why are the cops
looking for him?
I simply asked you to
take a picture of him.
Where the hell are you now?
We are at Gaema Plateau.
What?
You should've come with us.
Flowers are blooming and
Grandpa is very happy.
Then you really made it there.
He would've liked
you to come along.
OK, OK.
Come with us next time.
We're in North Korea.
We shouldn't be using cell phone...
- Of course. I'll hang up.
- Yes, Sir.
Let's meet tomorrow.
tomorrow...
Thank you.
Gab-Bun! Where are you?
I hear something.
- where?
- Just go
Hey, hey, hey, what are you up to?
We'll hide in here for a while.
What for?
You have no reason to but I have plenty.
So you should've
stayed away from trouble.
- get your ass in here.
- Alright.
Gab-Bun! Where are you? Gab-Bun!
Gab-Bun! Wait for me,
I'll come and find you.
Gab-Bun!
You are Gab-Bun, aren't you?
I thought you
were arriving yesterday.
You hungry? Come in.
You must be Gab-Bun.
You were here.
You came alone?
hat about Deok-Su?
I am Soo-Dong.
Deok-Su is the big brother?
I have no brother.
Yes. Where are you headed?
To Gaema Plateau.
Are you still single?
I have two kids.
Both went to Seoul.
Kids nowadays don't stay
in country with an old mother.
They went to Pyoungyang.
Fled to the South.
You've grown old.
You should stay here tonight.
I'm not going anywhere now.
Your eldest son is Chon-Su?
- Cheol-Su?
- Yes.
- Cheol-Su.
- His name is Chon-Su?
- Right. Chon-Su.
What's the matter?
Are you crying?
I am not crying? I have no tears
left being so close to my last days.
You miss Chon-Su?
You want to see his picture?
You have his picture?
- you want to see His picture?
- Yes.
Wait.
This little one.
He looks like me, isn't he?
He took after his mother.
Where di you get this watch?
You want it?
Chon-Su picked it up on the beach.
It doesn't even keep the time now.
It's very old. You can have it.
Why did you come so late?
How many time do I have to tell you?
A war broke, I barely survive.
The door doesn't open.
- Give it a good push... out of the way!
- It's locked.
See, it's locked.
There are people here!
Open the door!
- There are people here!
- Open the door!
'The first freight on railroad
Seoul - Pyoungyang - Paris.'