Subtitles made by RussianSubMaker
What’s with these dumb topics,
like “who’s bigger, is cooler?
Survival of the fittest, or what? Scared?
Not scared. How long?
Here
You think I didn’t see when we were swimming?
Last one there’s a smelly carpenter
(song): Out of boredom, learn lessons,
Today we’re not up for them.
Cosmos in the chest, baby,
The hertz of the heart exploded…
Между нами импульс тока...
Between us, an electric current impulse...
Why’s our door open?
Look
Looks like someone’s on our roof
We should probably get her down
Wait. She’s gonna flip over and flash her tits. Just watch
Sure
That one’s [amazing]
For sure! What’re you talking about?
I’m telling you! I can see it from here
Have you lost it?
Who would stare at you? Who even needs you,
you big-eared thing?
Are you dumb?
You’re lucky I don’t hit people with crooked legs
Let him go!
Take your hands off!
Say it! Zhenya excuse the dumbass
Go to hell! Asshole
Just try
It’s from East Germany.
And he’s from the USSR. Let him go!
He should apologize first
Быстро извинись, засранец.
Да пошла ты!
Wait!
This roof is for those who live here!
We moved here last week, got it?
So what? Get lost
Hey San'
You leave, or was that not enough?
Damn, Ilyukh, who did this to you?
Tsigan's [Gypsy’s] gang
There’s a letter for you
Damn it.
But we don’t go to their neighborhood anymore
They took my cat hostage
Said if we don’t bring the cash
That they will shit on her
Let them, we’ll never save up for the boat at this rate
Give me my share
I’ll go handle it myself
Are you serious?
You pay to walk around?
Yes.
Who’s that?
Nobody. Why you listening in?
Go keep sunbathing
Go on, keep sunbathing
Listen here
Careful
What careful?
Starting tomorrow, pay me for the roof
Buzz off
We need to pay them the money
Yeah, so they can see us as losers for the rest of our lives.
I’m fed up with it
Got a different plan?
Yes, I do
I’ll hit Tsigan.
One punch, and he’ll never come back
They’ll catch us one by one, and that’s it.
We need a compromise
Just say you’re scared.
Let’s go, Ilyukh, get your cat
Why’re you tagging along like a little dog?
I just want to watch them beat you up
Hey
Just go home
There are real thugs there.
I’ll handle it without you
You know why she followed us?
She’s into me
Really?
I’m telling you, when she twisted my arm,
I felt her chest with my back
Where are you from?
We moved from Kazakhstan
Cool.
What’s the mortality rate over there?
Haven’t checked
We’ve got a high death rate
Make it not too strong, you know, for the first time
Stop playing around.
Acting like a fag
Dad said, two bags per glass of water
That’s how we’ll do it
Tsigan
Guys, wait, I’ll be right back
Hey, brothers! Want to drink some chifir [strong tea] with us?
No, no, thank you
Why not?
A decent guy offers you a drink, and you’re acting like you’re too good for us?
No, you got it wrong
What do you mean, I misunderstood?
Are you calling me stupid?
Hold up, Koschei.
Let him speak
So, I brought the cash, just like you asked
What? I asked?
So, you think I’m an extortionist?
Are you accusing me?
I made the decision myself.
Alright, go ahead, since it’s your choice.
Like, he came in here throwing accusations
How much?
A thousand
Actually, it was fifteen hundred.
He pocketed five hundred, I saw it
What? How about I empty my pockets right now, and if there’s nothing, I’ll punch you in the face
Deal?
I saw it too
Saw what, exactly?
Quiet, quiet
The guys are dealing fair, right?
Right
Can I take the cat?
What?
A cat? This one?
Yeah.
Well, dance.
Leave him alone, he can’t dance
Hey, was anybody asking you there?
Dance!
Op op
Fifteen hundred is for three
But there are four of you.
Look, there’s a chick with you
Her? She’s not with us
Not with you?
Well then, sit with us, yeah?
Hey, redhead, come here
No need.
Don’t be scared, bro! We’re nice guys
What are you standing there for? I said come here!
Wait a second.
What’s your problem, huh?
Hey, what are you doing, idiot?
What, feeling brave, six against two?
I could take all of you one-on-one...
Well?
Tsigan
(shouting)
You bastard! You ruined the chifir, you bitch!
(music playing): Alone again,
awake at night, flipping through my past
Above me, the voice of the night
circles in the air, unhidden
This is all because of you and your stupid cat
(song playing): My
precious, my pain,
my precious, I’m yours, only
heaven knows how much I love you
My precious, my life,
my precious, I’m yours...
What?
Suck my ass, you fools!
Жень
Open the door
Open the door, I said!
Come out, don’t be scared! We won’t
touch you!
Girl, hey girl? Let’s go
Bro, I said, open the door
Come on out, schoolkids! Hey, we’re gonna
tip over your car! Come out
Come out, I said!
Wait, wait, wait!
Yeah
Where did you learn to drive?
Well, my granddad taught me once
Well, I think we’ve lost them
You’re not as much of a fool as you seem at
the first glance
Thanks
Iluh,
They killed your cat
No, she was already dead.
I was taking her to bury her
You know who you are?
Ilyusha
A big one!
Listen, how about we drive to my place?
Okay, let’s go
(music playing)
Oh, Doctor Alban
Stop, fridge, stop, freezer...
(singing): It’s my life...
It’s my love, my life
My life
(mom talking on the phone off-screen): I’m telling you,
no, in '62 the pipe burst
Well, then hurry up and leave
What am I supposed to do with your bronchitis?
The hot water’s leaking, you’ll breathe in some steam too.
What, another accident?
Yep
That's it
Nadusha, we agreed,
no smoking in the house, it’s harmful
Listen, Fedya, that’s not proven
Fifteen years ago
Your dad sent me a picture of himself on a donkey
With the caption: "I’m the one on top."
Thanks to this wonderful little clarification
Our happy family was born
Fedya, thank you so much
Happy holiday!
Dad, mom, I also have a gift for you
Okay, let’s see.
Let’s see
Fedya, I also have a gift for you
Really?
Raya died
Who?
Dummy. Raya, on the left, remember? The woman
who sold lingerie at the market
I made an arrangement with Vitalik,
You’re going on Saturday
Me?
At the market, selling
Fedya, you have no idea, this is a real chance
I made twice as much
this weekend as I did in half a year
At the housing and utilities.
Song!
Were whiter than snow
Wedding flowers
This is humiliating
Fedya, your salary is like five of these chickens,
and honestly, that’s humiliating
Nadush...
We’ll earn twice as much,
just the two of us
Please, I ask you, I’ve already arranged everything
(singing): Wedding flowers
still live within me
Mom, dad, happy wedding anniversary
Come on, bunny
Nadya, about the market...
I am not going
Hooray!
Why are you sitting?
Look at yourself, what a scarecrow you've become.
What’s that on your face?
Seriously, can’t you just get rid of all this?
Wait,
What’s that?
Tripped.
What?
And this is how you tripped?
Alexander, Ryabinins don't lie
Just don’t be angry
Well, well, well
It’s nothing
It’ll heal by the wedding
Alright, we leave Vika
at home, and now we go to the police, okay?
Why rush, maybe no one
even saw him?
Did anyone see you?
Listen, what difference does it make if anyone
saw him or not
You see, you have a son who’s a thief
And he should take responsibility
for his actions, understood?
Mom.
Mom..., I’m going to mom you now, mom
If they give him a real sentence, they’ll send
him to a juvenile detention center
Listen, what are you talking about?
They won’t send him, understood?
Spit it out
Let’s go
Maybe we should call your brother?
We’ll ask for advice
I’ll call my brother right now.
I’ll call him right now
The prison is crying for him, for my brother
Why are you sitting down?
Let’s go!
Fedya, where are you going?
Uh...
My stomach hurts a bit
Fedya, we’re waiting for you downstairs.
Ah
So, who was the mastermind behind the hijacking?
Me
Accomplices?
Lastnames?
Names, Nicknames?
No, I was alone
Are you sure?
According to witnesses, there were two teenagers
in the car
Sasha, I don’t understand who you’re protecting
I’m telling you, I was alone
The car owner has shown up
Very good
Let him wait in the hall for now
So what’s the deal?
Zurab Otarovich?
He’s going to die
If you don’t water him, he’ll die
Yes, sir,
we’ll keep an eye on it
Wait,
where are you going?
Fedya!
Wait,
what’s going on here?
Where’s that faggot
Hey, you piece of shit,
sit down!
Do you know whose car you stole?
I will fuck you, then will fry your ears and eat them
I stole it.
What?
Sasha!
Timur
Excuse him.
Timur really loved that car
I have a grandson,Khryzon
want to leave him a city
without thieves.
You know...
You know, we deeply
regret what happened
Your son?
This is my son
And mine
He is ours
Your son destroyed
my nephew's car
Now you have to buy him a new one
And there was money under the seat. Ten grand
I didn’t take any money
He broke the car,
but he didn’t take the money
No,no, he didn’t take the money
You heard him, he said...
The money needs to be returned
How can we return it?
We don’t have that kind of money
Sell the apartment.
Borrow
The deadline is in a week
Later, for every overdue
day, I’ll cut off one of his fingers.
I can always be found at the "Caucasus" restaurant.
Wait.
Please, wait.
Sorry...
Excuse me.
Who, who are these people?
What people?
I didn’t see anyone.
How?
Don’t make fools
out of us.
Wait, are you mocking us?
You saw it, just now
there were people here.
They, you know, they threatened him.
They threatened my child.
They said they would cut him
off every day.
We will sue you.
Please, calm down.
Your case is closed.
The Kamaz driver wrote that he crashed into
a pole.
And the BMW owner has no claims.
You are free to go.
How?
Nadya, I’m sure everything will be fine.
Sasha, just don’t worry, we’re changing the toilet for the former colonel
of the militia...
Is that Uncle Alyk here?
Well, hello, Zurab.
Afghan?
You shouldn’t have stopped. Start the engine.
Don’t rush.
They say your car got smashed?
How do you know?
Afghans have eyes everywhere.
Let me fix it—
no questions asked.
Fix it.
But what about the money?
Ten thousand bucks disappeared from the car.
Small change, Zurab.
What about a hundred?
Not a lime.
I personally didn’t see that money.
Your word
against mine?
Anyway, Zurab,
I'll fix the car, but the money...
I respect your word.
But there’s no evidence.
Sorry.
As you wish.
You won’t give it—I’ll ask them.
Did you call him after all?
What, Nadya, how could I?
It’s just a lucky coincidence.
Sancho, you’re something else, nephew.
What are you even doing?
What do you need?
Me? Nothing.
I talked with the chebureks, made the deal for you
with the car.
What about?
I’ll fix their car, and everything will be fine.
We don’t need your help.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Oh, what have I done! Zurab Jan, let’s rewind everything.
It’s not funny at all, understood?
Come on, smile, sis.
You already have wrinkles.
Dumbass
Friends, how about coming to our place?
We’ll have some tea, eat some chicken legs.
And in the end, Ali has not been
here for a long time.
How much do we owe you?
One thank you will be enough.
Thank you.
We don’t need gangster money.
We’re an honest family with a reputation.
And we won’t owe anything
to people like him. How much?
A thousand bucks.
Ups.
Nadya.
I’ll pay everything.
With a receipt.
Give me the passport number and don’t forget
the stamp.
You...
just unbelievable.
Where are you going?
You’ll send it by mail.
Sancho, Uncle Fyodor, hold on.
Don’t you want to visit your father?
(music playing)
So, what’s up?
Mommy, this is my piggy bank.
My sunshine, of course,
it’s your piggy bank.
But you see, right now we’re in a very
complicated economic situation in the family.
And for this, you should thank your brother.
Here’s your brother, say thank you.
And also, my sunshine, we really need
some money.
But your dad, for some reason, just doesn’t want to.
He doesn’t want to make money.
Well, because he’s very proud.
And he has his favorite thing to do.
And all the dirty, hard work is done by
mommy,
my sunshine! Right.
What do we have here?
Let’s see.
Aha.
Earrings, do you like the earrings?
Nice earrings.
Look, I like them too.
We’ll have to sell them.
Do you like the bracelet?
I like it too.
I also like this bracelet.
We’ll have to sell it too.
And the grandfather’s medal too, of course,
we’ll have to sell it.
We’ll have to sell all of this.
My sunshine,
forgive me, please, okay?
It’s okay, it’s okay, don’t cry, come here.
Nadya.
I’ll go with you to the market to work.
(song playing): The rebellious spirit,
Pandora’s dream
Poisoned arrows.
A fire in the chest
Couldn’t
Destroy the spell...
You’ll take this, and he’s under house
arrest.
Mom, why just a little pancake?
Eat, bunny.
Okay, go ahead.
Have a good day.
Goodbye.
Here, take it, I don’t
want it.
Dad.
Well?
Let me take the receipt myself.
You don’t need to get involved in this, San.
You shouldn’t have gotten in the car, and
gone under the bridge.
Yeah.
I shouldn’t have.
Hello, Baba Manya, Baba Tonya.
(song playing): Drunken stars burned,
Bullets sang, blood poured.
They died for fun,
Resurrected, fought again...
Come on, come on, let’s go.
That’s it.
No more flirting with the salesgirls at the market, understood?
That’s it, hook,
only for a month.
You’re kind, Oleg, I would’ve shot his balls for that.
What?
Go.
You’re so ruthless.
Alick. Alick.
Commander, damn! Some kid just
got here, says he’s your nephew.
Didn’t get it.
Do you have a nephew?
I’m seeing him for the first time.
San, confirm it.
Maybe there’s something I don’t know about you?
Maybe you have a wife?
Yeah, I’m a eunuch.
I was, until I met you.
Sancho, you’re a saboteur.
Sorry, I didn’t mean to.
You’re free.
What?
Aah..Yes!
Lift up your jacket, my arms can’t bend.
Yuri...
Close the door.
Good news.
The fifth and sixth chapters of my novel
are ready.
Do you remember, I gave you to read?
I don’t remember, but can you still
show it to your publisher friend?
I really need the money.
It’s such a lively story.
I would thank you from the advance.
I’ll wash my hands. It’s okay, I’ll reprint it again.
Fedya, I don’t need an opus about Ivan
Sergeyevich. Do you understand or not?
Ah, so you’ve read it. Well, how did you like it?
Honestly?
Yeah.
Here.
So what! He writes shitty poems himself.
Fedya, I hear everything.
This is how we do it...
Understood.
Let’s toast to the meeting.
Here, the guys from Astrakhan sent this.
Come on, come on, come on! You don’t know how to live beautifully.
Bye.
I also hate this caviar.
Donald!
Sanyok, do you have a girlfriend?
No.
It’s fixable.
Yeah, he has everything.
He stole a car for her.
Mmm, how cool.
Nobody stole a car for me.
Hey, hello.
Vitek, it suits you.
So, Vitek,
do you like it when they grab your ass?
Uncle Alik,
take me with you.
I have to work off this debt myself.
What?
You want to live like this?
Yes, I’m ready to do anything.
Just not criminal stuff.
Don’t worry, we’ve already killed Zurab.
So your family thinks this about me too, right?
I don’t think so.
Here’s a letter from my mom.
I’ll work it off myself.
Come on, Sancho,
go home.
Chew gum, drink soda, live life to the fullest,
while I’m alive, I’ll protect you.
Don’t rush to grow up.
No, I...
I want to do it myself.
I’m ready to sweep courtyards, wash cars.
Anything.
Go home, or your proper
mom will yell at you.
So, kid,
time to go home?
I don’t need your gum.
Come on, come on.
Fedor Ivanovich,
I’m here again.
You didn’t submit the Life of Archpriest Avvakum.
I don’t have any life story.
Lost it?
Well, look for it more.
I’ll come back to you tomorrow.
Uh-huh.
If you don’t find it, it’s not a big deal.
I’ll mark it as worn out.
Fedor Ivanovich, something happened?
To me?
No. No, everything’s fine.
I just thought I was a writer.
Turns out I’m just
an ordinary hack.
And my place is in the market.
What are you saying?
It can’t be that,
that a person with such
a love for literature as you
writes badly.
You...
haven’t read it.
So let me read it.
I’ll honestly, impartially
tell you how talented you are.
Yes. Let's do it.
Thank you, Tatyana.
You can just call me Tanya.
Tanya.
Sorry, what do you need?
Maybe I can do something?
I want to make up for my screw-up in front of Uncle Alik.
You need to, you make up for it.
Please, I'll do anything.
Listen, do you see the Shishik parked there?
What?
Over your shoulder.
Gas 66.
There are boxes of canned food, you need to unload it.
We need an empty truck by evening, urgently.
Alright, I'll do it.
Well, why are you just staring, the Gas is over there.
Thanks.
No problem.
Fyodor Ivanovich.
Yes.
Yes, I'm here.
Are you the new Pikul?
Are you Marques?
I meant to say, are you the new Marques?
Come on.
Marques.
Now I...
Now, my favorite part.
If love could be measured with a thermometer,
their apartment would have long been covered
with a thin silver shawl of frost.
You... You
feel loneliness so accurately. You...
You... You feel loneliness so well.
I can't, I'm gonna cry.
Oh no, don't cry, don't cry.
Don't cry, I mean...
You don't need to cry,
and I don't want you to cry either.
Please, don't cry.
Fyodor Ivanovich, may I
kiss you?
Not as a man, as a genius.
Sure.
Why not?
On the cheek, on the cheek, is that okay?
Yes, just...
don't call me a genius.
I'm just an ordinary writer.
Fyodor Ivanovich, your novel...
The world must see it.
Really?
No, the front struts are bent,
consider it done for.
It'd be easier to get a new one from Germany.
And ten thousand bucks?
Let the suckers take the bait.
Well, by their standards, it's a screw-up.
They can claim it.
Let them try.
If they come after me, well'll fuck them like we did a year ago.
And what if they go after my guys?
I'll send a couple of fighters with RPGs, and that's it.
The Zurabs will go back to the mountains with their pockets full.
No, we don't need that war right now.
War, commander, never ends.
Once we bend, they'll keep fucking us for life.
That's it, Uncle Alik,
I've done everything.
I unloaded the truck.
I don't get it.
Which truck?
And where?
I took it to the warehouse.
Good job! Bring it back.
How come?
Sancho,
we just loaded it to take to the nursing home.
Hold on! Where are you going, stop. I'll get you home
Hey, who's gonna load the food back?
Yeah, damn belt buckle.
Alik, let's go to three wins.
Commander.
Just don't pinch my nipples.
(music plays)
Thanks, Uncle Alik.
Sancho!
Turbulent times are starting.
Here, you'll be defending the family.
Seriously?
No robbing stalls, don't dig your nose with a gun.
(male voice): So, I tell him:
"Hey, you got the wrong guy?"
Well, our guys showed up then. (female laugh)
Oh, Fedya's here.
Here, husband.
Fedya, meet Vitalik.
Hello.
Nadyukha says you're going in for Raika tomorrow?
Rest in peace.
By the way, I congratulate you on your anniversary.
You really got lucky with your wife.
Nadyukha, well, I’m off.
I won’t make it for the night. Well, go ahead.
Well, go, husband.
Your cardigan is
a bomb.
Exactly like this, they buried Raika.
Nadyukha, be careful with your things.
See you tomorrow.
Nadyu. What’s up?
Who's this character? This is our boss.
Well, really, you'll get used to it.
Mom, Dad.
I didn’t give you the gift yesterday.
Yeah. This is for you.
Thank you.
Sorry, Mom.
Okay.
Let's go have some tea.
Hi. Hi.
Looks nice, huh? Yeah.
Well, sit down, what are you standing for?
Listen, sorry I left you. It's just...
If Dad had found out, he would have torn my legs off.
It’s okay, I would’ve left you too if I hadn’t lost consciousness.
Want some beer? But I’ve never drunk.
Me neither, so what?
Huh?
It probably tastes good.
Yeah.
Can I ask you something? Yeah.
Yesterday, when I was sunbathing, did you stare at me for a long time?
No, we didn’t stare.
Yeah.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Oh, what’s this? You’re drinking without us, huh?
Ugh, what kind of crap is this?
Expired or something? How does my dad even drink this, here.
Anyway, you won’t believe it,
we were saving a dead cat yesterday. And then we were with this idiot on the go
on the train - wow!
What about you guys? What do you have?
The car was stolen!
(music plays)